【声音】
[SOUND].
【笑】
>> [LAUGH]
啊内容提供器
>> Content providers.
恭喜大家，你们已经完成构建Sunshine应用。
>> Congratulations, everyone, you've finished building the Sunshine App.
但总有空间给更多的阳光。
>> But there's always room for more sunshine.
是的Dan，但是现在是时候
>> There is, Dan, but now it's time
让学生去构建他们最终的项目了。
for the students to go build their final project.
你们可以从Android开发者网站上
>> And you can get a lot of the resources you
获得构建一个超赞的应用所需的许多资源。
need to build really great mobile apps at the Android developer site.
也可以从我们和Udacity这儿获取更多。
>> And stay tuned for more from us and Udacity.
现在，我想
>> For now, I think it's
是时候来些蛋糕庆祝一下了。
time to celebrate with some cake.
哇欧。
>> Woohoo.
柠檬挞。
>> Lemon tarts.
【音乐♪】
[MUSIC]